Department of Judicial Affairs Records UA211
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Department of Judicial Affairs Records
1988 -- 1999
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Division of Student Affairs
Department of Judicial Affairs
Undergraduate Education, Student Affairs and Student Services
UA211
1.75 Linear Feet 2 boxes
This collection consists of records created by Judicial Affairs within the Division of Student Affairs.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Office files; and Student files.
Custodial History
Materials were recovered from the vault in the basement of Ballou Hall in the summer of 2010.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of records, including office and student files, created by Judicial Affairs within the Division of Student Affairs.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Student Affairs and Services; Student life
- Office files, 1998 -- 1999; UA211.001; 0.55 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of office files from the Department of Judicial Affairs.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged by subject.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Veronica Carter, 1999; UA211.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Task Inventory & Role Definitions, 1999; UA211.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Department Task Inventories, 1999; UA211.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Department Task Inventories, 1999; UA211.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Training Documentation, 1999; UA211.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Change Management and Communications, 1999; UA211.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Visio Project- Student Development Project, 1999; UA211.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - New Process Maps- June 14, 1999; UA211.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Student Development, 1999; UA211.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Priority [empty], UA211.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Training Documents, 1999; UA211.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Student Development [1of4], 1999; UA211.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Student Development [2of4], 1999; UA211.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Student Development [3of4], 1998 -- 1999; UA211.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Student Development [4of4], 1999; UA211.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Student Life Sub Committee, 1999; UA211.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Gabrielle and Veronica, UA211.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Project Information: Tasks-Career SVS; Dos, Advise, 1999; UA211.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Student Development Committee Project, 1999; UA211.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Student Development Team, 1999; UA211.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
- Student files, 1988 -- 1996; UA211.002; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists of files of suspended and expelled students. Files were previously housed in the vault in Ballou Hall.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  75 years from the date of creation.
  - Student files, 1988 -- 1996; UA211.002.002.00001 (Box 2)
    Due to highly confidential nature of materials, this box is only cataloged to the container level.